const mondai = [
    { number: 1, question: '489 + 512 =', answer: '1001', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 2, question: '567 + 435 =', answer: '1002', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 3, question: '345 + 658 =', answer: '1003', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 4, question: '589 + 415 =', answer: '1004', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 5, question: '589 + 416 =', answer: '1005', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 6, question: '486 + 520 =', answer: '1006', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 7, question: '476 + 531 =', answer: '1007', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 8, question: '598 + 410 =', answer: '1008', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 9, question: '789 + 220 =', answer: '1009', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''},
    { number: 10, question: '463 + 538 =', answer: '1001', image_name: '', answer2: '', etc_2: '', etc_3: '', etc_4: ''}
];